Digital Media Department Collection
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Events, 2009 May 16-2016 July 14; nam_ua395-6; 93.44 GB 67737 Digital Files
  - Events, 2009 May 16-2016 July 14; nam_ua395-6.1; 75.21 GB 56337 Digital Files
    - Marvin Press Event_SOB_business climate, 2010 February 23; nam_ua395-6.1_516; 58.1 MB 77 Digital Files
    - Policy Conversation with SUNY Chancellor, 2010 March 2; nam_ua395-6.1_517; 104.2 MB 129 Digital Files
    - Chartwells Food Show_10, 2010 March 10; nam_ua395-6.1_518; 90.5 MB 143 Digital Files
    - Friends Exhibit, 2010 March 10; nam_ua395-6.1_519; 42.3 MB 60 Digital Files
    - Friends Exhibit, 2010 March 10; nam_ua395-6.1_520; 42.3 MB 60 Digital Files
    - Michael Brennan Lecture, 2010 March 11; nam_ua395-6.1_521; 41.7 MB 62 Digital Files
    - Refuge Conversation Progam, 2010 March 12; nam_ua395-6.1_522; 54.6 MB 70 Digital Files
    - Middle States Evaluation Team, 2010 March 17; nam_ua395-6.1_523; 57.6 MB 74 Digital Files
    - Theresa Pardo_CTG_Brown Bag Lunch, 2010 March 18; nam_ua395-6.1_524; 40.6 MB 85 Digital Files
    - ASP, 2010 March 18; nam_ua395-6.1_525; 58.0 MB 79 Digital Files
    - Census_hand print event, 2010 March 23; nam_ua395-6.1_526; 74.2 MB 170 Digital Files
    - Howard Dean_Karl Rove_Debate, 2010 April 7; nam_ua395-6.1_527; 297.0 MB 647 Digital Files
    - Howard Dean_Karl Rove_Debate, 2010 April 8; nam_ua395-6.1_528; 297.0 MB 647 Digital Files
    - Howard Dean_Karl Rove, 2010 April 8; nam_ua395-6.1_529; 101.4 MB 186 Digital Files
    - Burton Lecture, 2010 April 20; nam_ua395-6.1_530; 115.3 MB 218 Digital Files
    - Earth Day Events, 2010 April 22; nam_ua395-6.1_531; 72.0 MB 82 Digital Files
    - President's Breakfast with Business Leaders, 2010 April 23; nam_ua395-6.1_532; 46.1 MB 101 Digital Files
    - Awards of Excellence, 2010 April 23; nam_ua395-6.1_533; 31.1 MB 50 Digital Files
    - Fountain Day 2010, 2010 April 26; nam_ua395-6.1_534; 951.1 MB 497 Digital Files
    - Fountain Day 2010, 2010 April 26; nam_ua395-6.1_535; 951.1 MB 497 Digital Files
    - Fountain Day 2010, 2010 April 26; nam_ua395-6.1_536; 951.1 MB 497 Digital Files
    - Connecting the Dots Planning for Education, 2010 April 27; nam_ua395-6.1_537; 8.8 MB 16 Digital Files
    - Vital Volunteer Luncheon, 2010 May 1; nam_ua395-6.1_538; 66.5 MB 147 Digital Files
    - Great Dane Awards, 2010 May 3; nam_ua395-6.1_539; 80.6 MB 171 Digital Files
    - Bread and Roses, 2010 May 6; nam_ua395-6.1_540; 35.7 MB 87 Digital Files
    - Hindelang Lecture, 2010 May 12; nam_ua395-6.1_541; 17.6 MB 42 Digital Files
    - Torch_Photo Service, 2010 May 13; nam_ua395-6.1_542; 39.6 MB 77 Digital Files
    - Time-Dollar Program, 2010 June 7; nam_ua395-6.1_543; 61.5 MB 138 Digital Files
    - United Way_Arbor Hill, 2010 June 10; nam_ua395-6.1_544; 18.1 MB 45 Digital Files
    - Sexual Assault Conference, 2010 June 22; nam_ua395-6.1_545; 61.4 MB 163 Digital Files
    - Small Business Forum with Rep. Paul Tonko, 2010 July 8; nam_ua395-6.1_546; 65.4 MB 85 Digital Files
    - IFW_2010, 2010 July 15; nam_ua395-6.1_547; 23.5 MB 26 Digital Files
    - Cancer Center Summer Students, 2010 July 23; nam_ua395-6.1_548; 105.2 MB 273 Digital Files
    - Fullbright Gateway_2010, 2010 August 9; nam_ua395-6.1_549; 7.9 MB 7 Digital Files
    - Giants Scholarship recipient, 2010 August 17; nam_ua395-6.1_550; 29.0 MB 46 Digital Files
    - Explore UAlbany Program, 2010 August 27; nam_ua395-6.1_551; 19.0 MB 38 Digital Files
    - Explore UAlbany_Pres. Philip and Mayor Jennings, 2010 August 27; nam_ua395-6.1_552; 132.2 MB 117 Digital Files
    - MPA Welcome event_panel discussion, 2010 August 27; nam_ua395-6.1_553; 163.6 MB 85 Digital Files
    - Virtual Media Guide, 2010 August 30; nam_ua395-6.1_554; 113.0 MB 187 Digital Files
    - Welcome Back Pizza Party, 2010 August 30; nam_ua395-6.1_555; 59.3 MB 53 Digital Files
    - Hannah's Hope_Sames Family, 2010 September 2; nam_ua395-6.1_556; 72.3 MB 138 Digital Files
    - SEFCUmoneymachine_Explore UAlbany, 2010 September 3; nam_ua395-6.1_557; 12.4 MB 18 Digital Files
    - Karen Hitchcock Portrait Unveiling, 2010 September 17; nam_ua395-6.1_558; 169.7 MB 321 Digital Files
    - SPH_25th Anniversary Open House, 2010 September 24; nam_ua395-6.1_559; 93.4 MB 183 Digital Files
    - reception for visiting researchers, 2010 October 6; nam_ua395-6.1_560; 15.3 MB 35 Digital Files
    - Alumni Awareness Luncheon_10, 2010 October 8; nam_ua395-6.1_561; 61.6 MB 149 Digital Files
    - Scholarship recipients and donors, 2010 October 8; nam_ua395-6.1_562; 90.6 MB 226 Digital Files
    - freelance, 2010 October 9; nam_ua395-6.1_563; 1.4 GB 1082 Digital Files
    - SA_Barbara Walters, 2010 October 9; nam_ua395-6.1_564; 222.4 MB 281 Digital Files
    - Legacy Reception, 2010 October 9; nam_ua395-6.1_565; 1.4 GB 1082 Digital Files
    - Business Leaders Breakfast, 2010 October 26; nam_ua395-6.1_566; 99.8 MB 172 Digital Files
  - 2015 Welcome Week Events, 2015 August 21-2015 September 26; nam_ua395-6.2; 0 MB 0 Digital Files
  - Commencement, 2009 May 16-2016 June 16; nam_ua395-6.3; 8.42 GB 5742 Digital Files
    - Commencement, 2002 December 8; nam_ua395-6.3_1; 223.6 MB 40 Digital Files
    - Alumni Affairs: 5/15/04 @ 5:30 - 6:30 PM location TBA Precommencement Dinner / Legacy, 2004 May 18; nam_ua395-6.3_2; 46.4 MB 30 Digital Files
    - Alumni Affairs: 5/15/04 @ 5:30 - 6:30 PM location TBA Precommencement Dinner / Legacy, 2004 May 18; nam_ua395-6.3_3; 46.4 MB 30 Digital Files
    - Commencement: 12/11/05 @ 2 PM RACC December Commencement, 2005 December 27; nam_ua395-6.3_4; 436.1 MB 122 Digital Files
    - Commencement: 3/23/06 @ 9:30 AM studio Grads in Gown_ Christy Smith and Brian Goodale, 2006 April 6; nam_ua395-6.3_5; 70.3 MB 65 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/8/06 @ 4:45 PM studio three students in commencement robes for web feature, 2006 May 23; nam_ua395-6.3_6; 50.8 MB 48 Digital Files
    - Commencement: 11/6/06 @ 10 AM to retake photos of Brian Goodale and Christy Smith of the Graduate Studies Office with UAlbany's Official regalia with new robes with a slight color change in the University seal., 2006 November 6; nam_ua395-6.3_7; 123.3 MB 53 Digital Files
    - Commencement: 12/10/06 @ 1 PM RACC for Winter Commencement ceremony, 2006 December 10; nam_ua395-6.3_8; 78.7 MB 215 Digital Files
    - Rockefeller College: 5/20/07 @ 12:30-2 p.m. Milne Hall, Downtown Campus for Commencement Ceremony, 2007 May 21; nam_ua395-6.3_9; 81.3 MB 166 Digital Files
    - Commencement: 5/19/07 @ 9 AM SEFCU Area for Graduate Commencement Ceremony 5/20/07 @ 10 AM Lawn of the Science Library for Undergrad Commencement Ceremony, 2007 May 21; nam_ua395-6.3_10; 176.0 MB 363 Digital Files
    - Commencement: 5/19/07 @ 9 AM SEFCU Area for Graduate Commencement Ceremony 5/20/07 @ 10 AM Lawn of the Science Library for Undergrad Commencement Ceremony, 2007 May 21; nam_ua395-6.3_11; 176.0 MB 363 Digital Files
    - University Events: 12/9/07 from noon till 3:30 p.m. to take photos of December commencement., 2007 October 25; nam_ua395-6.3_12; 139.3 MB 297 Digital Files
    - President's Office: 10/11/07 at 2:30 to take shots of Fall Faculty meeting in the Campus Center., 2007 October 25; nam_ua395-6.3_13; 25.8 MB 43 Digital Files
    - University Events: 12/9/07 from noon till 3:30 p.m. to take photos of December commencement., 2007 October 25; nam_ua395-6.3_14; 139.3 MB 297 Digital Files
    - University Development: Photo session: 5/17/08 at 9:00 AM in the SEFCU Arena for Graduate Commencement Photo session: 5/18/08 at 10:00 AM at the Science Library lawn for Undergraduate Ceremony, 2008 May 17; nam_ua395-6.3_15; 2.4 GB 478 Digital Files
    - Rockefeller College: Photo session: 5/18/08, 12:30-1:30 PM for Undergraduate Commencement at Rockefeller College, Page Hall., 2008 May 18; nam_ua395-6.3_16; 736.3 MB 130 Digital Files
    - Commencement Reception_School of Ed, 2008 December 8; nam_ua395-6.3_17; 24.6 MB 33 Digital Files
    - Commencement Brunch, 2008 December 8; nam_ua395-6.3_18; 17.4 MB 34 Digital Files
    - Winter Commencement 2008, 2008 December 8; nam_ua395-6.3_19; 514.2 MB 365 Digital Files
    - Winter Commencement 2008, 2008 December 8; nam_ua395-6.3_20; 514.2 MB 365 Digital Files
    - Lavender Graduation, 2009 May 15; nam_ua395-6.3_21; 93.0 MB 38 Digital Files
    - Graduate2009, 2009 May 16; nam_ua395-6.3_22; 136.1 MB 222 Digital Files
    - Undergrad_2009, 2009 May 17; nam_ua395-6.3_23; 308.7 MB 180 Digital Files
    - Undergrad_2009, 2009 May 17; nam_ua395-6.3_24; 196.4 MB 281 Digital Files
    - saved, 2009 December 7; nam_ua395-6.3_25; 608.7 MB 369 Digital Files
    - Winter Commencement 09, 2009 December 7; nam_ua395-6.3_26; 608.7 MB 369 Digital Files
    - Graduate Commencement2010, 2010 May 15; nam_ua395-6.3_27; 273.6 MB 310 Digital Files
    - undergraduate commencement2010, 2010 May 16; nam_ua395-6.3_28; 312.7 MB 436 Digital Files
  - Homecomings, 2013 October 19-2015 November 17; nam_ua395-6.4; 9.81 GB 5658 Digital Files
    - Homecomings, 2013 October 19-2015 November 17; nam_ua395-6.4.1; 9.81 GB 5658 Digital Files
      - Homecoming_08, 2000 February 3; nam_ua395-6.4.1_1; 1.7 GB 548 Digital Files
      - Alumni Affairs: 6/20/02 @ noon Milne 2nd Floor Alumni Anniversary Luncheon digital, 2002 July 4; nam_ua395-6.4.1_2; 71.6 MB 57 Digital Files
      - Alumni Affairs: 10/9/04 @ 12 Noon - 2 PM RACC Homecoming Tailgate Party and Game start digital, 2004 September 2; nam_ua395-6.4.1_3; 195.7 MB 127 Digital Files
      - Alumni Affairs: 10/9/04 @ 12 Noon - 2 PM RACC Homecoming Tailgate Party and Game start digital, 2004 September 2; nam_ua395-6.4.1_4; 178.6 MB 127 Digital Files
      - Alumni Affairs: 10/9/04 @ 4:15 - 5:15 PM Standish Room / Science Library Legacy Reception digital, 2004 September 14; nam_ua395-6.4.1_5; 66.0 MB 47 Digital Files
      - Alumni Affairs: 2/16/05 @ 7:30 AM Life Sciences Bldg. 2nd fl lobby breakfast and tour / alumns digital, 2005 January 25; nam_ua395-6.4.1_6; 87.7 MB 57 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 3/30/05 @ Noon CC Patroon Room Pres Hall with Student Athletes digital, 2005 April 13; nam_ua395-6.4.1_7; 20.6 MB 11 Digital Files
      - President: 3/31/05 @ 10 AM Wadsworth Lab / Corning Tower Albany, NY President tours Wadsworth Lab digital, 2005 April 14; nam_ua395-6.4.1_8; 107.2 MB 68 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 3/31/05 @ 2 PM Pres Office Channel 6 video taping; Business Forward digital, 2005 April 14; nam_ua395-6.4.1_9; 29.6 MB 20 Digital Files
      - Alumni Affairs: 4/9/05 @ 5:30 PM Desmond Hotel Latham, NY Milne / Alumni Event digital, 2005 April 20; nam_ua395-6.4.1_10; 158.6 MB 109 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 4/14/05 @ 12:30 Hall of Fame RACC Westchester area high school counselors w/ Pres Hall digital, 2005 April 20; nam_ua395-6.4.1_11; 26.5 MB 18 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 4/14/05 @ 12:30 Hall of Fame RACC Westchester area high school counselors w/ Pres Hall digital, 2005 April 20; nam_ua395-6.4.1_12; 26.5 MB 18 Digital Files
      - Alumni Affairs: 6/3/05 - 6/4/05 various times and locations Alumni Weekend 2005 digital, 2005 June 16; nam_ua395-6.4.1_13; 924.8 MB 505 Digital Files
      - Alumni Affairs: 10/8/05 @ various times and locations Homecoming_05 digital, 2005 October 17; nam_ua395-6.4.1_14; 261.0 MB 104 Digital Files
      - Advancement Events: 10/8/05 @ 9:30 AM Standish Room President's Champagne Brunch digital, 2005 October 18; nam_ua395-6.4.1_15; 279.4 MB 108 Digital Files
      - University Development: 12/20/05 @ 11AM Alumni House Potter Club Alumns, 2006 January 3; nam_ua395-6.4.1_16; 106.4 MB 18 Digital Files
      - Alumni Affairs: 10/20/06 - 10/21/06 various locations Homecoming 2006, 2006 October 10; nam_ua395-6.4.1_17; 709.7 MB 387 Digital Files
      - Alumni House: Homecoming 2007: Tailgate, Football game crowd shots and various Alumni class events / Sat. Oct. 13, 2007 from 3 - 9 p.m., 2007 October 14; nam_ua395-6.4.1_18; 298.1 MB 276 Digital Files
      - Alumni House: Homecoming 2007: Tailgate, Football game crowd shots and various Alumni class events / Sat. Oct. 13, 2007 from 3 - 9 p.m., 2007 October 14; nam_ua395-6.4.1_19; 298.1 MB 276 Digital Files
      - Homecoming_08, 2008 October 25; nam_ua395-6.4.1_20; 1.7 GB 548 Digital Files
      - Alumni Awards Gala, 2009 May 2; nam_ua395-6.4.1_21; 75.0 MB 181 Digital Files
      - Alumni Association, 2009 May 3; nam_ua395-6.4.1_22; 121.7 MB 167 Digital Files
      - Alumni Awareness Luncheon_09, 2009 October 10; nam_ua395-6.4.1_23; 474.2 MB 257 Digital Files
      - Alumni Awareness Luncheon_09, 2009 October 10; nam_ua395-6.4.1_24; 474.2 MB 257 Digital Files
      - Alumni Excellence Awards Gala, 2010 May 1; nam_ua395-6.4.1_25; 129.8 MB 285 Digital Files
      - Homecoming_Fall Festival, 2010 October 9; nam_ua395-6.4.1_26; 1.4 GB 1082 Digital Files
    - 2015 Homecoming, 2015 October 9-2015 November 17; nam_ua395-6.4.2; 0 MB 0 Digital Files
- Portraits, 2006 June 1-2016 July 15; nam_ua395-7; 28.07 GB 24688 Digital Files
  - Portraits, 2006 June 1-2016 July 15; nam_ua395-7.1; 6.63 GB 5819 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 3/28/03 @ 11:30 AM studio re-creation shot for case statement publication digital, 2003 April 11; nam_ua395-7.1_1; 4.9 MB 16 Digital Files
    - Ctr for Women in Government: 6/30/03 studio portraits of Directors digital, 2003 July 10; nam_ua395-7.1_2; 6.4 MB 10 Digital Files
    - Ctr for Women in Government: 6/30/03 studio portraits of Directors digital, 2003 July 10; nam_ua395-7.1_3; 6.4 MB 10 Digital Files
    - Portraits, 2003 August 7; nam_ua395-7.1_4; 22.3 MB 31 Digital Files
    - Portraits, 2003 August 7; nam_ua395-7.1_5; 57.5 MB 85 Digital Files
    - Portraits, 2003 August 7; nam_ua395-7.1_6; 25.8 MB 41 Digital Files
    - Portraits, 2003 August 7; nam_ua395-7.1_7; 22.3 MB 31 Digital Files
    - Portraits, 2003 August 7; nam_ua395-7.1_8; 8.9 MB 16 Digital Files
    - Portraits, 2003 August 7; nam_ua395-7.1_9; 8.9 MB 16 Digital Files
    - Portraits, 2003 August 7; nam_ua395-7.1_10; 57.5 MB 85 Digital Files
    - Portraits, 2003 August 7; nam_ua395-7.1_11; 25.8 MB 41 Digital Files
    - Business: 8/6/03 @ 1:30 PM Studio cover photo for viewbook transparency and digital, 2003 August 21; nam_ua395-7.1_12; 83.3 MB 126 Digital Files
    - Portraits, 2003 September 6; nam_ua395-7.1_13; 249.2 MB 84 Digital Files
    - Portraits, 2003 September 13; nam_ua395-7.1_14; 285.2 MB 113 Digital Files
    - Portraits, 2003 September 19; nam_ua395-7.1_15; 103.8 MB 88 Digital Files
    - Portraits, 2003 September 19; nam_ua395-7.1_16; 11.4 MB 9 Digital Files
    - Portraits, 2003 September 19; nam_ua395-7.1_17; 11.4 MB 9 Digital Files
    - Portraits, 2003 September 19; nam_ua395-7.1_18; 103.8 MB 88 Digital Files
    - Portraits, 2003 October 3; nam_ua395-7.1_19; 41.0 MB 36 Digital Files
    - Portraits, 2003 October 3; nam_ua395-7.1_20; 41.0 MB 36 Digital Files
    - Portraits, 2003 October 30; nam_ua395-7.1_21; 67.5 MB 27 Digital Files
    - Portraits, 2003 October 30; nam_ua395-7.1_22; 67.5 MB 27 Digital Files
    - Advancement: 1/7/04 @ 2:30 PM 25 East Bayberry Rd. Glenmont, NY portrait: Joy and Kenneth Ford digital, 2004 January 19; nam_ua395-7.1_23; 40.1 MB 35 Digital Files
    - Advancement: 1/7/04 @ 2:30 PM 25 East Bayberry Rd. Glenmont, NY portrait: Joy and Kenneth Ford digital, 2004 January 19; nam_ua395-7.1_24; 40.1 MB 35 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 6/16/04 @ 2 PM Clock Tower James Czebiniak and car digital, 2004 June 30; nam_ua395-7.1_25; 44.9 MB 24 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 6/16/04 @ 2 PM Clock Tower James Czebiniak and car digital, 2004 June 30; nam_ua395-7.1_26; 44.9 MB 24 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 6/16/04 @ 2 PM Clock Tower James Czebiniak and car digital, 2004 June 30; nam_ua395-7.1_27; 44.9 MB 24 Digital Files
    - Outreach: 7/12/04 @ 9;15 am 12 Sheridan Ave Albany Sharon Dawes w/ Tom Griffen digital, 2004 July 14; nam_ua395-7.1_28; 86.1 MB 62 Digital Files
    - Business: 8/26/04 @ 12:30 BA-220 MBA head shots digital, 2004 August 11; nam_ua395-7.1_29; 58.9 MB 192 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 8/3/04 @ 12:30 PM Schenectady, NY portrait: Carmella Batista digital, 2004 August 17; nam_ua395-7.1_30; 55.9 MB 36 Digital Files
    - Center for Legislative Development: 10/28/04 @ 10 AM 423 State Street portrait: Bob Nakamura digital, 2004 November 9; nam_ua395-7.1_31; 82.9 MB 71 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 11/1/04 @ 1:00 pm Cobb Room / Main Library portrait: Mr. And Mrs. Sheppard digital, 2004 November 15; nam_ua395-7.1_32; 39.4 MB 21 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 12/1/04 @ 1 PM Alumni House students with gonfalons and flags digital, 2004 December 13; nam_ua395-7.1_33; 103.7 MB 66 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 1/11/05 @ 2 PM CC 137 portrait: Nancy Bellowitch-Negron digital, 2005 January 25; nam_ua395-7.1_34; 44.1 MB 25 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 1/24/05 @ 1:30 PM Lecture Center Delores Cimini with students digital, 2005 February 7; nam_ua395-7.1_35; 59.6 MB 58 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 1/31/05 @ 3 PM 332 Loudonville Rd. Loudonville, NY portrait: Terri Boor and Ed Mayer digital, 2005 February 8; nam_ua395-7.1_36; 60.5 MB 41 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/19/05 @ 2 PM Parent's Fountain Mr. and Mrs. Shepherd / Mr. and Mrs. Ostoyich digital, 2005 June 2; nam_ua395-7.1_37; 97.1 MB 50 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/19/05 @ 2 PM Parent's Fountain Mr. and Mrs. Shepherd / Mr. and Mrs. Ostoyich digital, 2005 June 2; nam_ua395-7.1_38; 97.1 MB 50 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/19/05 @ 2 PM Parent's Fountain Mr. and Mrs. Shepherd / Mr. and Mrs. Ostoyich digital, 2005 June 2; nam_ua395-7.1_39; 97.1 MB 50 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/31/05 @ 11 AM Selkirk, NY portrait of Marie Wideman digital, 2005 June 14; nam_ua395-7.1_40; 114.6 MB 77 Digital Files
    - Research: 6/1/05 @ 10 AM studio photo for Research Report digital Kerry Gavin/Mary Fiess, 2005 June 15; nam_ua395-7.1_41; 42.8 MB 40 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 6/1/05 @ 11:30 studio Bonnie Steinbock digital, 2005 June 15; nam_ua395-7.1_42; 39.9 MB 85 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 7/14/05 @ 2:30 PM Freedom Quad Vince Porforio Digital, 2005 July 29; nam_ua395-7.1_43; 120.2 MB 79 Digital Files
    - President: 8/16/05 @ 1:15 PM Facilities Management Bldg. Service Bldg. B Chiller Photo Op digital, 2005 August 29; nam_ua395-7.1_44; 59.0 MB 37 Digital Files
    - President: 8/18/05 @ 11:30 AM Media and Marketing Office Suite Pres Hall presents Val DiRocco with winnings from horserace winnings digital, 2005 September 1; nam_ua395-7.1_45; 17.0 MB 11 Digital Files
    - Provost: 9/8/05 @ 9:00 AM - 10:30 AM Location TBA Compact Planning Workshop digital, 2005 September 1; nam_ua395-7.1_46; 58.0 MB 41 Digital Files
    - University Development: 8/23/05 @ 11:50 Giant's Practice Field portrait: Al Baker digital, 2005 September 6; nam_ua395-7.1_47; 29.8 MB 18 Digital Files
    - Business: photo sessen: 8/25/05 @ 12 Noon BA 220 MBA head shots digital, 2005 September 8; nam_ua395-7.1_48; 439.1 MB 177 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 9/7/05 @ 2:30 PM Collins Circle Tom Birkland attaching UAlbany decal digital, 2005 September 21; nam_ua395-7.1_49; 54.0 MB 36 Digital Files
    - ZAKHAR~1, 2005 December 8; nam_ua395-7.1_50; 25.5 MB 36 Digital Files
    - COVER, 2005 December 8; nam_ua395-7.1_51; 116.7 MB 57 Digital Files
    - MISC, 2005 December 8; nam_ua395-7.1_52; 5.6 MB 3 Digital Files
    - University Development: 12/5/05 @ 6 PM Pepper Jack's Restaurant (Western Ave and Quail St.) Alumnus owner w/ Pres Hall digital, 2005 December 13; nam_ua395-7.1_53; 120.1 MB 32 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 12/15/05 @ 11 AM Studio / campus location Patty Stahl / Honors College Brochure, 2005 December 26; nam_ua395-7.1_54; 270.6 MB 62 Digital Files
    - Evgeny Dikarev, 2006 March 22; nam_ua395-7.1_55; 189.8 MB 97 Digital Files
    - President: 4/18/06 @ 6 PM - 7:30 PM Pres Res reception / Hudson Valley Regional Artists Show, 2006 March 22; nam_ua395-7.1_56; 218.2 MB 95 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/18/06 @ 2 PM studio web feature: William Komaromi and Bill Lanford, 2006 June 1; nam_ua395-7.1_57; 57.7 MB 55 Digital Files
    - Library: 5/31/06 @ 2:30 PM Main Library Staff Photo, 2006 June 14; nam_ua395-7.1_58; 20.1 MB 11 Digital Files
    - Business: 9/8/06 @ 10 AM 411 State St. Portrait: Gail Berley, 2006 September 22; nam_ua395-7.1_59; 323.9 MB 198 Digital Files
    - Albany Institute for Research in Education: 10/4/06 @ 9:30 am ED B9 portraits; 3 facilitators, 2006 October 9; nam_ua395-7.1_60; 99.0 MB 57 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 11/2/06 @ 1:30 PM in front of Biology Building for photo of Jessica Campbell for a web feature., 2006 November 2; nam_ua395-7.1_61; 92.6 MB 52 Digital Files
    - Center for Women in Government & Civil Society: 1/12/04 @ 1 - 3 p.m. Draper Hall Room 105 for headshots of 16-17 people attending., 2007 January 12; nam_ua395-7.1_62; 277.4 MB 147 Digital Files
    - Judaic Studies: 3/2/07 @ 2:45 PM HU 355 for photos of staff, students w/books and plaque for UAlbany Magazine., 2007 March 2; nam_ua395-7.1_63; 58.4 MB 39 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 11/16/07 at 9:30 in studio to take portrait shot of Fathima Farheen for web story., 2007 November 28; nam_ua395-7.1_64; 30.3 MB 75 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 1/29/08 @ 10:30 LOB 532 / NYS Assembly Albany, NY Internist Donna Yee, 2008 February 11; nam_ua395-7.1_65; 98.2 MB 126 Digital Files
    - President's Office: Photo session: 5/12/08 @ 11:30 a.m. with Steve and Mike Ammann for the Annual Report., 2008 May 12; nam_ua395-7.1_66; 57.7 MB 127 Digital Files
    - David Smith and Hany Shawky, 2009 February 25; nam_ua395-7.1_67; 11.1 MB 26 Digital Files
    - Kane, Carrie, 2009 March 11; nam_ua395-7.1_68; 36.7 MB 48 Digital Files
    - Prof. Bakhru and student, 2009 March 20; nam_ua395-7.1_69; 40.3 MB 64 Digital Files
    - Affinito, Stephanie, 2009 March 26; nam_ua395-7.1_70; 150.4 MB 181 Digital Files
    - Alex Shekhtman, 2009 March 31; nam_ua395-7.1_71; 101.1 MB 59 Digital Files
    - year in review portraits, 2009 May 1; nam_ua395-7.1_72; 120.0 MB 149 Digital Files
    - Chittibabu Guda, 2009 August 12; nam_ua395-7.1_73; 48.5 MB 76 Digital Files
    - Doug Conklin, 2009 August 12; nam_ua395-7.1_74; 58.5 MB 77 Digital Files
    - Tom Begley, 2009 August 13; nam_ua395-7.1_75; 116.8 MB 195 Digital Files
    - Roxana Moslehi, 2009 August 13; nam_ua395-7.1_76; 57.4 MB 77 Digital Files
    - Kutchukian, Winifred, 2009 August 25; nam_ua395-7.1_77; 76.2 MB 119 Digital Files
    - Blevins, Jimmy, 2009 September 5; nam_ua395-7.1_78; 15.6 MB 15 Digital Files
    - Zahn, Evan, 2009 October 24; nam_ua395-7.1_79; 14.7 MB 43 Digital Files
    - Novkov, Julie, 2009 October 31; nam_ua395-7.1_80; 41.0 MB 38 Digital Files
    - University Council Members, 2009 November 14; nam_ua395-7.1_81; 25.0 MB 61 Digital Files
    - Kelly Virkler, 2009 November 25; nam_ua395-7.1_82; 29.6 MB 57 Digital Files
    - Joseph and Diedre Zimmerman, 2010 March 18; nam_ua395-7.1_83; 14.8 MB 43 Digital Files
    - Harris, Hope, 2010 April 21; nam_ua395-7.1_84; 26.6 MB 30 Digital Files
    - LaKe'Sha and Chym Bowen, 2010 May 11; nam_ua395-7.1_85; 40.8 MB 78 Digital Files
    - Anderson, Ian, 2010 June 3; nam_ua395-7.1_86; 121.6 MB 198 Digital Files
    - Asker, Courtney, 2010 July 14; nam_ua395-7.1_87; 195.7 MB 426 Digital Files
  - Faculty Staff, 2006 June 1-2016 July 6; nam_ua395-7.2; 13.29 GB 12345 Digital Files
    - Ctr. For Compartive Genomics: 10/10/01 @ 9:30 AM East Campus/ B231 staff photos for website digital, 2001 October 24; nam_ua395-7.2_1; 32.0 MB 53 Digital Files